Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
- Hello?
- Hello.
Is Cristina there?
No. she's not available.
May I take a message?
Uh. yeah. well. um...
Yeah. sorry. I'm a friend
from her group...
Oh. shit.
From her shit?
Um...
Look. just tell her I'm from group.
I'm Charlie.
She's got my number.
Oh. she goes to your group?
I shouldn't have. um...
Look. just tell her
Charlie called.
And I will do
exactly that. Charlie.
once you tell me what kind
of group we're talking about.
- Is it AA? NA?
- Look...
You sound exactly like
she describes you.
Uh.
does she talk about me in group?
I don't think I
can really talk about that.
What does she say about me?
Well. she loves you very much.
What does she love about me?
Oh. okay. Well...
She loves that you're creative.
You love art
and TV and movies.
Okay. well.
lots of people love movies.
Yeah. but she says
you love scary movies
and that you guys
have that in common.
She's proud
of making a fan out of you.
- She is?
- Yeah.
Well. she told me the other
day. she wonders...
what's your favorite
scary movie?
Uh... The Babadook.
It's an amazing meditation
on motherhood and grief.
Isn't that
a little fancy pants?
Well. it's elevated horror.
Uh-huh.
What does that mean. "Elevated horror"?
You know. it's scary but with complex
emotional and thematic underpinnings.
It's not just some schlocky. cheeseball
nonsense with wall-to-wall jump scares.
Hmm.
Sounds kind of boring to me.
Have you ever seen Stab?
Once. I think.
At a sleepover
when I was. like. 12.
You live in Woodsboro
and you don't know Stab?
Your mother loves that movie.
She talks about it
all the time in group.
How well do you remember
the original?
I don't know.
I mean. it was super '90s.
It was really over-lit
and everyone had weird hair.
Uh-huh.
Do you remember the beginning?
Not really.
It started with
a kill scene. right?
They always started
with a kill scene.
Yeah. that's right.
That's right.
It's a girl at home. alone.
She answers a wrong number and
starts talking with the killer
who makes her play a game.
Would you like to
play a game...
Tara?
All systems armed.
This isn't fucking funny. Amber.
I told you. this isn't Amber.
Amber's looking
particularly fetching tonight.
She really shouldn't leave her phone
lying around for anyone to clone.
What do you want?
I told you.
I want to play a game.
Stab movie trivia.
three rounds.
You call the cops.
she dies.
You get a question wrong.
Her parents aren't home.
I can be in that room
in 15 seconds.
You want a warmup question?
I told you
I don't know these movies!
Ask me about something
I do know.
Ask me about It Follows.
Ask me about Hereditary.
Ask me about The Witch.
In the first Stab movie.
what Woodsboro native
was introduced
as the franchise's
main character?
It's Sidney Prescott!
It's Sidney Prescott
and she lived on Elm.
Correct. You see.
you're gonna do great at this.
Okay. question one...
No. I got that one right.
It should count.
Anyone could have
gotten that one right.
Sidney's in every movie
but the last one.
Question one:
Who wrote the original book
that the Stab movies
are based on?
Um... Um...
The... The chick from TV!
"The chick from TV"
is not gonna cut it. Tara.
Gale Weathers!
It is Gale Weathers.
you motherfucker!
Correct.
Amber might live
to see the sunrise.
Question two: Who played the dumb
bitch in the beginning of Stab 1
who answers the phone and
gets carved up by the killer?
Fuck you.
Is that the answer
you're going with?
A non-answer
counts as a wrong answer. Tara.
Time's running out.
Ticktock. ticktock.
ticktock. ticktock...
Heather Graham!
Correct!
You pulled that one out.
Now for the final question:
Who was the killer in Stab 1?
Oh. I know this one. you fuck.
It's Billy Loomis!
It's Billy Loomis.
and he was Sidney's boyfriend.
he was played by Luke Wilson.
and I got you. asshole!
I got it! I got it right!
Oh. I'm sorry. Tara.
but that's just not correct.
What?
No. no. it is. It is.
That is right.
The correct answer
is Billy Loomis and Stu Macher.
There are two killers
in the original Stab.
I'm afraid someone's
got to die now.
No. no. no.
Amber. I'm coming.
Fuck. fuck. fuck.
All systems armed.
The police are on their way.
asshole!
All systems disarmed.
All systems armed.
- All systems disarmed.
- Oh. my God. No.
All systems armed.
All systems disarmed.
Hello?
Bonus question. Tara.
Please stop.
Do you think
I made it inside your house
before you could rearm?
Help!
No! No. no. no!
Excuse me. miss?
- What'd you just take?
- Your boner pills.
Good luck getting it up now.
You. um...
You are my boner pills.
No. No.
You okay?
Yes.
You don't have to check on me all the time.
I'm not breakable.
Yeah. this I know.
Shit.
- Sam?
- Hey. What's going on?
Uh. Tara...
was attacked.
What? Is she...
She's alive.
but in bad shape.
She was...
stabbed.
- Stabbed? What the fuck?
- She made it through surgery
and the doctor
said it went well.
She's resting now.
I know you guys
aren't on the best terms. but...
I'm on my way.
She's gonna be okay. Sam.
We'll see you soon.
- Hey. wait. Wes!
- Yeah?
Do they know who did this?
It's probably better
if you just come here.
Wes.
She said it was someone
in a fucking Ghostface mask.
My sister was attacked.
I gotta go.
Wait. hey! Hey. hey hey.
I'm... I'm going with you.
- No. No. Richie...
- No. Sam. I'm coming with you.
- Okay.
- Okay. Yeah.
Attention. Panthers.
A reminder that all classes
and school activities
are canceled tomorrow
due to public safety concerns.
That was Sam.
- She's coming?
- Yeah.
Watch everything get worse.
All I'm saying is.
with everything going on right now.
I think it's time we take our relationship
to the next. most intimate level.
He wants me to accept
his Find My Fam request.
It's the smartest option with
a would-be killer on the loose.
You know exactly where I am and
I know exactly where you are.
Aw. you can stalk me
like a jealous boyfriend.
And you can stalk me
Is this because you two
aren't having sex yet?
You bring up a very good point.
Not that I want to sound
like a stereotypical jock
- trying to get into his girl's pants...
- Great!
Don't do it. Liv.
There's a psycho out there.
You make yourself
harder to find.
Delete social media.
tape over your phone camera.
disable GPS.
Yes. thank you very much.
Edward Snowden.
Actually. your mother just interrogated
me about Tara's attempted murder.
which was very fun.
I'm sure she's asking everybody.
I mean. Ghostface is back.
The press
still isn't saying Ghostface.
My mom doesn't want
to cause a panic.
It'll get out by the second
or third killing.
Jesus. Mindy. there wasn't
a first killing. Tara's alive.
- Mmm. I mean. she could still die.
- What the fuck?
Or the killer
could come back for her.
Fuck! Mindy. come on.
I'm just telling you.
arm up. okay?
Pepper spray. check.
Taser. check.
Girlfriend repellent. check.
Nice. Thank you.
Holy shit.
Is that... Vince?
Wait. The creep
you hooked up with last summer?
- Yeah. He worked with me and Tara.
- He worked with Tara?
He's been stalking my Instagram
the last couple weeks.
posting the creepiest shit.
Probably time to introduce him
to Hobbs and Shaw.
Maybe not the best idea
to incite violence
right in front
of the sheriff.
Looks like he's leaving.
Thanks anyways. boys.
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Hmm. Tara says
she fought back hard.
You've got bruises.
It's from football practice.
- Oh. sure.
- Tara's awake. She just texted.
I'm going to the hospital.
You guys coming?
- Yeah.
Oh. uh...
I can't.
but I'll meet
you guys there.
All right.
- I've actually never seen Stab.
- You've never seen Stab?
- Mmm.
- Not even the one that came out last year?
I've never seen
Gone with the Wind either.
but I don't consider it. like.
a huge hole in my cinematic education.
Most of the Stab movies are based
on things that happened here.
Define "things."
Things like...
a guy named Billy Loomis
and his friend
carved up a bunch
of high-school kids
while wearing
this Halloween ghost mask.
You mean like
in Halloween?
- No. Not like in Halloween.
- Oh.
Sounds a lot
like Halloween.
- All right. it's a little like Halloween.
- Okay.
And every decade or so.
some idiot gets the bright idea
to put on the mask. kill his
friends. and get famous too.
The last time it happened
was in 2011.
And we came here
voluntarily?
Well. I got to make sure
Tara's okay.
Right. Yes. of course.
And I got to make sure we don't
get sliced up by some lunatic
who saw Friday the 13th and
thought. "You know what?
That Jason guy.
he's got some pretty solid ideas."
Can I ask you
one question though?
Yeah.
Do you have any idea why
someone wearing that mask
would want to kill your sister?
No.
How are you feeling?
You came.
Of course I came.
This is my boyfriend.
Richie.
It's so nice to meet you.
I'm so sorry if I'm intruding.
Nice to meet you too.
Hi.
- Thank you for calling.
- Of course.
Look at your hair!
I like it.
These are Chad and Mindy.
the twins. And Wes.
I used to babysit them all.
Which is always how
I like to be introduced.
And Amber. Hey.
Hi. Nice to see you.
Hi. I'm Richie.
Hi.
Where's Mom?
She's stuck
at a conference in London.
She called me earlier.
Yeah. for all of ten minutes.
Uh. look. guys.
Tara's really tired.
Maybe we should
just give her some space.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
Not you. Sam.
I want you to stay.
Okay.
- But the rest.
- Yeah.
If it's okay with you.
I could sleep here tonight.
I'd really like that.
Okay.
- Do you have your extra inhaler?
- I'll be fine.
Okay.
Bye.
- Okay. I'll be right outside.
- Thank you.
Bye.
Sam.
I was so scared.
I know. It's okay.
So what is she like.
the sister?
Sam?
Oh. Sam is so cool.
You only say that
because she let you
wear Pokémon onesies
to bed for a year.
True. That's a true statement.
No. trust me. Sam is not cool.
Her dad left her mom. right?
Walks right out when Tara's
eight. Sam's 13.
Sam started acting out.
getting in trouble with the cops.
And then. on Sam's 18th
birthday. she leaves.
Ghosts them all.
Maybe Sam's changed.
I just don't want
to see Tara hurt again.
So what. you're protecting Tara
from her own sister now?
Well. someone has to.
Okay. so no guys
are good enough for her.
and now her family's
off-limits too?
Mmm. motive.
"If I can't have her.
no one can."
What?
We know
you have a crush on Tara.
Okay.
Come on. Mindy.
But we're all suspects.
- Except maybe Liv.
- Thank you.
You're way too boring
to be a psycho.
Yo. Liv.
You want a real drink?
Or are you happy sitting
at this kids' table?
Listen up. uglier Michael
Myers. it was a summer fling.
- It meant nothing.
- Was I talking to you?
I don't care
who you're talking to.
- Liv. let's go.
- Don't talk to her!
I don't want to hear
your voice.
- Shut the fuck up.
- Hey!
Get out of here
or I'm calling the cops.
Go!
- I'll see you soon. sweetheart.
- Hey. man. fuck you.
You kids too! Let's go!
Do you see this shit?
Fuck this bar. man.
Fuck you.
Fuck it!
What the fuck?
Is that you. pretty boy? Huh?
Get out of my fucking car!
Hey.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Just a bad dream.
What are you watching?
Oh. Stab is on Netflix.
What?
I want to be prepared.
I got to go
find something to eat.
Yeah. okay.
How you doing. Sam?
Mmm. Antipsychotics aren't working
as well as they used to. are they?
Fuck you.
You can't run
from who you are. Sam.
I'm just trying to help.
Hey. when are you gonna tell her
why all this is happening?
Blue team. ICU.
Hello.
Hello. Samantha.
Who is this?
Someone who knows
your little family secret.
You're the fuck
who hurt my sister?
Oh. she's not
the only one I'm gonna hurt.
I had to get you to come
back here somehow. didn't I?
You want to fuck with me.
asshole?
I'm right here. Come and get me.
With pleasure.
Help!
Help! Help!
Somebody help me!
He's trying to kill me!
What's going on?
You're okay.
Somebody tried to kill me
in the break room!
I've got a body
outside a bar on Main.
and now you get attacked here.
You said the call came
from Amber's number?
So? We know he cloned my phone
before when he attacked Tara.
Or. and I'm just
spit-balling here...
you're the killer.
And where were you
when all this happened?
I was...
watching Netflix.
- Yeah. Super-solid alibi. bro.
- So where were you?
I was questioning her
at the sheriff's station.
Yeah.
I came as soon as I heard.
But. you know.
the Netflix alibi is good. too.
Both of you.
stop it.
You're gonna put more cops
on her room. right?
Yes.
And I can move you
to a private floor.
Deputy Vinson knows what he's doing.
You'll be safe.
Like we've been so far?
Samantha.
let's step outside.
Nice to see you.
Deputy Hicks.
- So many fun memories.
- It's "Sheriff" Hicks.
I remember you too...
and all the trouble
you used to cause your family.
Your presence here
is not helping.
So maybe when the sun comes up.
you and your boyfriend
can hit the road
and leave it to people who
actually care about this community.
Well.
she remains a delight.
Are you okay?
Um. would you mind
giving us a second?
I need to talk to Tara.
Come on. Netflix.
Let's go.
Do you remember
when Dad left?
Parts. sure.
I was eight. I don't know what
that has to do with anything.
It has to do with it.
Do you remember how...
Mom used to keep those boxes
up in the attic?
Well. I was up there once.
when I was 13.
looking for Christmas presents.
And I found these old diaries
that she kept from high school.
- Sam. what is...
- Please.
I just... I have to do this.
So I found these old diaries.
And I knew it was wrong.
but I read some anyway
because Mom got pregnant
with me in high school.
and I thought it could be cool to
find out how she and Dad got together.
How romantic
it must have been.
So I read some.
Only it wasn't romantic.
Mom was dating Dad. but...
she was in love
with this other guy...
and he got her pregnant.
She told Dad it was his.
and that's why
he proposed senior year.
Sam. what are you talking about?
And I'm sitting there.
in this attic.
and I'm 13...
and I just found out
my dad isn't my dad.
So I go find Mom in her bedroom.
and I'm screaming at her
and shoving this diary
in her face.
and I didn't even realize...
that Dad was standing
right behind me.
He didn't know.
He found out right then from me.
He left that night.
I'm the reason he left.
No.
- No. Sam...
- Mom never forgave me.
Then she made me promise never to
tell you because you were so young.
And that's why I changed
and I got distant
and weird with you.
And I went out
and I started doing
every drug
that I could get my hands on
until I couldn't take it anymore
and I left town.
I just couldn't be
around you anymore. Tara.
Not only because I destroyed
our family that night.
but because...
those diaries told me
who my real father was.
It was Billy Loomis.
And somebody knows.
and I think
that's why you got hurt.
And I'm so fucking sorry that I
never told you and that I ran away.
- I'm so sorry.
- Get out.
Tara.
You're gone
for five years...
Five whole years.
And then I get stabbed
and you want to come back
and drop
all this shit on me?
- I thought I was protecting you.
- Protecting me from what?
The truth?
No.
- No. I... Please. Tara.
- Sam.
- I need you to get the fuck out.
- I'm so sorry.
- Sam.
- Please.
Get the fuck out!
Hey. hey. It's okay. it's me.
Were you listening
at the door?
No. no.
of course not.
Okay. yeah.
I was listening at the door.
It doesn't freak you out...
that my real father
was a serial killer?
I mean...
yeah.
A great deal. yeah.
Okay. well. then go.
I get it.
I just got to stay
and figure it out.
I'm not leaving you here. Sam.
You know that part
in horror movies
where you want to yell
at the characters to be smart
and get the fuck out?
This is that part. Richie.
You should get the fuck out.
But I'm staying.
I love you.
- You're such a dumbass.
- I'm such a dumbass.
So...
your sister won't talk to you.
The police aren't gonna help.
What's our next move?
We go talk to an expert.
...temperatures
here Tuesday. Wednesday in the mid-50s.
and then finally we'll see those
mid-60s returning next week.
Just one night after a
local teen was attacked in her home
by an assailant
wearing a Ghostface costume.
Sheriff Judy Hicks has now confirmed
two more late-night attacks
that have left Woodsboro
reeling.
The first victim.
Vincent Schneider.
was found dead behind
the Corner Pocket Pool Hall.
A second victim.
as yet unnamed.
was attacked inside Woodsboro General
Hospital. but escaped without injuries.
Needless to say. Woodsboro
is on high alert today...
Live from Studio
1-A in Rockefeller Plaza...
Good morning.
I'm Gale Weathers.
Before we dive in.
I want to tell you a little story
that happened on the way
into the studio this morning.
I stopped to get a bacon...
...at a bodega. already
a quintessentially New York...
Go away!
Sorry to bother you.
Mr. Riley!
We just want to ask you
a few questions.
I don't give interviews.
We're not looking
for an interview.
Give me one good reason
why I should talk to you.
I'm Billy Loomis's daughter.
That's a terrible reason
for me to talk to you.
My name is Samantha Carpenter.
I was attacked last night
at the hospital.
The night before that.
my sister was stabbed seven times.
I know you know
what that's like.
I'm just trying
to protect my family.
Five minutes.
That's all I'm asking.
I'll give you
two minutes.
I'm missing a show I like.
...bangs again.
stage an intervention.
Gale Weathers.
- Weren't you two. um...
- Yeah.
Who's he?
Oh. this is Richie.
my boyfriend.
How long have
you known him?
Six months?
Did he know who your dad was
when you met?
Express any interest
in Woodsboro
or the Ghostface killings?
What the hell
are you talking about?
Your killer's obsessed
with the Stab movies. right?
Well. there are certain rules
to surviving a Stab movie.
Believe me. I know.
Rule number one:
Never trust
the love interest.
They seem sweet. caring. supportive.
Then welcome to act 3.
where they're trying
to rip your head off.
I was with Sam in Modesto
when Tara was attacked.
And let me guess.
you were just in the other room.
conveniently unaccounted for when
she was attacked at the hospital.
Okay. do I have to take this from
shitty Sam Elliott over here. or what?
Rule number two...
...the killer's motive is always
connected to something in the past.
- I'm related to Billy.
- Right.
but then why kill
that random Vince guy?
That's for you
to figure out.
And rule number three.
and this is the most important rule:
The first victim always has a friend
group that the killer is a part of.
Does your sister have a
close-knit group of friends?
Yeah.
She does.
Then look for the killer there.
If you can find out
why they're doing this.
you can figure out
who's next.
So help us.
Help us figure out
who is behind this.
You kidding me?
I've been stabbed nine times.
I've got permanent nerve damage
and a fun little limp.
You think I want
to do that again?
You just said it always goes
back to the past. right?
So if I'm in danger...
that means you're in danger.
Come on.
Let's do this together.
Your time's up.
Jesus!
Yeah. he's way more fun
in the movies.
Okay. uh.
what's next?
The friends.
Thanks so much for that. Kevin.
Coming up after
our local weather.
the pros and cons of
reuniting with old friends.
Hello?
Hey. Sid. it's me.
Dewey?
Oh. my God.
How long has it been?
I'm just trying to get a run in
before I take the girls to school.
How are you?
I'm good.
really good.
How are you?
How's Mark?
I think I'll keep him.
How are things
in the sheriff's business?
Uh. they're...
- They're fine. But. Sid...
- Have you talked to Gale lately?
No. Not in a couple years.
I know things didn't end well
with you guys. but...
Sid...
it's happening again.
What are you talking about?
Some idiot in a Ghostface mask.
Three attacks so far.
One dead.
Something about this one
just feels different.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
you know me.
Yeah.
I do. That's why I'm asking.
I'm fine.
I just...
want you to be safe up there.
Do you have a gun?
I'm Sidney fucking Prescott.
Of course I have a gun.
Good. That's good.
Does Gale know?
No. she's my next call.
But. Sid. promise me:
No matter what you hear
or what you see on the news.
don't come here.
No offense. Dewey.
I have no intention
of ever setting foot
in that town again.
Good.
Dewey...
whoever this killer's after.
I'm glad they have you to protect them.
But...
you be safe. okay?
Will do.
It's good to hear your voice.
You too. Sid.
Come on.
Get it together. Dewey.
Probably shouldn't
have sent the smiley face.
Holy shit. He came.
I've decided to temporarily
assist you in your investigation.
Thank you.
Look. just because
that guy showered
doesn't mean
he should have a gun.
- Yeah.
How do you know
so much about the Stab movies?
Runs in her family.
Randy was our uncle.
RIP.
You said to bring everybody.
Hey.
Ooh. suspects!
My brother
would be so proud.
Hey. Martha.
Dewey! Hi!
You look...
Yeah.
How's the wife?
Mom. we're good.
Thank you.
All right. kids.
have fun.
I asked Mindy to call everybody
here. because...
there's something
I have to tell you.
Let me get this straight.
You're saying that you're
the daughter of Billy Loomis.
and. what.
that one of us is the killer?
The killer told me
he knew my secret.
He attacked Tara
to lure me back here.
But then why
immediately go and murder
some douche-nozzle
that was stalking Liv?
And why
does it have to be one of us?
What about Deputy Dewey here?
Maybe he's the killer.
No offense.
None taken.
but what's my motive?
You got stabbed a billion times.
got dumped by your famous wife
and crawled into a bottle.
I think it's safe to say
you're on the suspect list.
Well. maybe you're the killer.
Because that cut deep.
That douche-nozzle
is connected.
I googled him.
His mom is Leslie Macher.
- Stu Macher's sister.
- Who's Stu Macher?
He's Billy Loomis's accomplice.
A real loony tune.
Okay. Okay.
So the first three attacks are all on
people related to the original killers.
Oh. my God.
He's making a requel!
A what?
Or a legacyquel.
Fans are torn
on the terminology.
Please speak English.
Remember the Stab movie
that came out last year?
Oh. yeah!
The one the Knives Out guy
directed?
I actually really liked
that one.
Of course you did.
You have terrible taste.
I hate you.
The point is. the hard-core
Stab fans hated it.
You go on 4chan
and Dreadit.
all they're talking about
is how Stab 8
pissed on their childhoods.
How they crammed in social
commentary just to elevate it.
How the main character's
a Mary Sue.
- What's a Mary Sue?
- You really don't want to know.
What's wrong
with elevated horror?
I mean.
Jordan Peele fucking rules.
Uh. obviously.
but that's not Stab.
Real Stab movies are meta
slasher whodunits. full stop.
- Come on. It's just a movie.
- No. it's not.
To some people. the original is
their favorite thing in the world.
The movie that made them
love horror.
That Mom or Dad showed them when they
were ten that bonded them together.
And God help anyone who slightly
fucks with that special memory.
Who makes a movie
they think disrespects it.
It sounds like our killer is
writing his own version of Stab 8.
but doing it as a requel.
Which is?
See. you can't just reboot a
franchise from scratch anymore.
The fans won't stand for it.
Black Christmas. Child's Play.
Flatliners...
That shit doesn't work.
But you can't just do
a straight sequel. either.
You got to build something new.
But not too new.
or the Internet goes bug-fucking nuts.
It got to be part
of an ongoing story line.
even if the story shouldn't have
been ongoing in the first place.
New main characters. yes.
but supported by and related to
legacy characters.
Not quite a reboot.
not quite a sequel.
Like the new Halloween. Saw.
Terminator. Jurassic
Park. Ghostbusters...
fuck. even Star Wars!
It always. always goes back
to the original!
Are you telling me that I'm caught
in the middle of fan-fucking-fiction?
Not just in the middle. Sam.
You're the star.
So. not to put
too fine a point on it.
but. according
to requel rules...
...who's next?
Going by the pattern.
whoever it is has to be connected
to someone that came before.
I'm starting
to regret coming here.
Jesus. my mom was
a character in one of them.
No one cares about the shitty
inferior sequels. Wes.
You're safe.
With Randy as our uncle. though.
you and I are probably screwed.
- Wait. What?
- Or you're the killer.
and this whole elaborate monologue
is just to cover your tracks.
I think it's pretty clear
who the killer is at this point.
Who?
You.
What...
It makes perfect
requel sense.
- That actually does make sense.
- Yeah.
Fuck this.
- Meet you back at the motel.
- Sam. wait.
Sam. wait.
The first fucking rule of
these movies is don't split up!
The nerve of that girl.
right?
Really not
in the mood right now.
Sam. Sam. Sam.
There is a killer
on the loose.
He's threatening you.
He's threatening your sister.
Are you gonna run away from
who you are like you always do.
or are you gonna use it?
I'm not like you.
Really?
Then how else
are you gonna survive?
I say accept who you are. let's get
out there. find out who's doing this.
and cut some
fucking throats!
No!
Mmm. And extra edamame.
Please.
Thank you.
I'll be there in ten minutes.
Bye.
That you. tiger?
Jesus!
Are you being safe out there.
honey?
To the point that
all my friends mock me. yes.
Good boy.
What's for dinner?
Sushi. I was just leaving
to pick it up.
Oh. Why don't you
just Postmates it?
Oh. it gets all smooshy
by the time it's here.
I know you hate that.
- Go shower. I'll be back soon.
- Okay.
- Can you put this away for me?
- Yes.
Okay.
- Love you.
- Lock the door.
- I will.
Sheriff Hicks.
Hello. Sheriff Judy.
- Who is this?
- I think you know.
I'm a fan of scary movies.
And knives.
What's your favorite
scary movie?
I prefer animated films
and musicals.
Why are you doing this?
I'll tell you all about it.
I'm calling to turn myself in.
I think that's a great idea.
We'll sit down at the station.
and I'll tell you about
the two people I've killed.
You've only killed one person.
By the time I see you.
I'll have gutted your baby boy.
No.
Whoa.
Fuck you!
Pick up. Wes!
This is Sheriff Hicks.
I need units to converge
on my house ASAP.
Copy that. We're on it.
Can't get him
on the phone. can you?
He must be busy.
How do I know
you're anywhere near him?
Ever seen the movie Psycho?
Please...
don't hurt my boy.
Why not?
- He's a good kid.
- Is he. now?
He never hurt anyone.
That's not enough.
Please! I'll do anything!
You're not gonna
make it in time. Sheriff Judy.
Wes!
I'm coming!
Help!
Okay.
Mom?
Fuck... you!
Miss. you can't be here.
You can't be here.
No. I'm sorry.
I know her son.
- Her son. Wes. Is he...
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Oh. my God.
You're...
Well. you're you.
Last time I checked.
Are you okay? You seem like
you're having a bit of a moment.
Did you know the sheriff?
Sort of.
She didn't like me very much.
She didn't like me either.
Um... I'm Samantha.
Sam. Carpenter.
My sister and I were attacked.
Oh. Sorry to hear that.
I'm Gale...
Riley.
Weathers. I'm Gale Weathers.
Excuse me.
Gale?
- A text?
- Ow.
You tell me the killer is back
in a text?
- Ow. that hurts.
- Good!
- You were on the air.
- How do you know?
A hunch.
You look good.
Are you still writing?
No time.
You were always happiest
when you were writing.
Well. sir. it's okay.
We're here with Gale.
I'd give you a hand.
but I can't release anybody right now.
Couldn't resist a good story.
could you?
Don't be an idiot. Dewey.
I'm here
because I was worried about you.
Okay. yes.
My producers wanted me to cover
this. for obvious reasons.
but 90% is because of you.
Well. I feel 90% better.
Don't be so sensitive.
Since when did you care
about my feelings?
Especially not
in the last couple years.
All right. listen. Let's not pretend
I'm the one who ended things.
No one's pretending. Gale.
I remember what happened.
Why aren't you in uniform?
I retired.
Since when?
Since they asked me to.
Oh. Dewey.
I don't need your pity. Gale.
I made my choices.
So did you.
It was my turn.
It was a great opportunity.
- You said you'd try.
- And I did.
For two whole months!
Listen. if you want to make me
feel worse
than I already do.
good luck.
The mornings aren't so bad.
'cause I get to see you.
Pretend I'm still back there
in New York.
But then I remember...
that I couldn't hack it.
I left
in the middle of the night...
like a coward.
Why wouldn't you
tell me that then?
It would have mattered.
You are a lot of things.
Dewey...
but you are not a coward.
You just...
You just were meant to be
in Woodsboro.
And you weren't?
Promise me you'll leave
as soon as you can.
You know I can't promise that.
I'm sorry about Judy.
Yeah. me too.
But she'll make a great chapter
in your next book.
And don't even get me started
on Ghostface's
signature new weapon.
That shit is lit.
And can we talk about
the title? Stab?
What. just like the original?
Just call it Stab 8.
It's fucking Stab 8.
You're not fooling anyone.
It's such bullsh...
Where have you been? You okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
That Mindy girl wasn't kidding.
Stab 8 is not like the others.
I mean. no connection
to the other movies.
- No legacy characters at all.
- Richie.
If you ask me. this franchise goes
off the rails with number five.
Richie. listen to me.
He killed two more people.
Wes and his mother.
He killed the sheriff?
You can do that?
I mean. are you okay?
Where are you?
- I'll call you right back.
- No. Sam...
Who's at the hospital?
Who's watching my sister?
I just heard about the sheriff.
They needed me here!
- Where are you going?
- My sister's in trouble!
...where Judy Hicks
has just been brutally murdered.
What are you waiting for?
Drive!
Come on. Let's go!
- Are the doors locked?
- Yeah. we should check.
Joey and Pacey. check the front door.
Jen and Cliff. get flashlights...
- Where you going?
- Hello?
You stay there.
No. I'm coming with you.
Okay.
He's got you.
Hello?
No. I'm not.
Please. Quit tripping out.
This is just Dawson
up to his old tired tricks.
There's no psychopath
in this house.
Yes. there is.
And you brought her.
Fuck this.
Fuck!
Oh!
Goddamn it!
Should you really be making
a phone call right now?
Please. please.
Stop! You know we have to live
through this to help her. right?
Just hold on.
Holy shit.
Ow! Ow.
- Goddamn it!
- Richie?
What are you doing here?
Sam called. She said that...
you were in trouble.
- Did you hit me with the phone?
- Look out!
Richie!
- Are you at the hospital?
- Hello. Samantha.
Richie can't come
to the phone right now.
He's finding out what happens
to people
who stick their noses in business
that doesn't concern them.
- Please don't hurt him.
- Tell you what. You can choose.
I'll only kill one.
What? What? Tera!
Who do you want to hear die?
No. Please! I'm begging you.
Please don't hurt them.
Really?
You can't save your own sister?
All you have to do is say.
"Kill Richie."
No!
Tara! Don't touch her!
Please. please. please.
I'm begging you.
Or say. "Kill Tara."
and I'll make sure to hit all
the organs I missed last time.
- No!
- Fuck you!
I'm begging you.
Please don't hurt her.
Last chance to save one.
Choose!
Why are you doing this?
You want to know why. Sam?
Maybe it's because
you're a selfish bitch
who can't even make a decision to
save the life of someone you love.
Maybe you're too weak
for this franchise.
Maybe you're right.
Or maybe I'm just
stalling for time. fuckhead.
I'll get Richie.
Tara!
Oh. my God!
Come on.
It's okay. I got you.
It's gonna be all right.
Get the elevator!
Not today.
Richie.
- Come on. hurry up.
- Oh!
- The head.
- What?
You have to shoot 'em in the
head. or they always come back.
Dewey!
Who gives a fuck?
- I do.
- No! Dewey!
Yes. today.
It's an honor.
No!
No! No!
I'm sorry.
I didn't know him well. but...
he helped me.
That's what he did.
He helped people.
I should've stopped him.
If you had.
my sister would be dead.
Samantha. your sister's awake.
Gale.
Sidney.
I came as soon as I heard.
I'm so sorry.
You shouldn't be here.
You shouldn't be here either.
- Mark and the kids are okay?
- Yeah. they're safe for now.
I'm here to make sure of that.
Come here.
How you feeling?
Every time I get attacked.
they give me better painkillers.
So there's that.
I'm sorry.
For what?
You saved my life.
For not telling you
sooner.
For being the reason Dad left.
You're not the reason Dad left.
You didn't choose where you
came from. Or who you came from.
I don't blame you for that.
I blame you for leaving me too.
That's never gonna happen again.
I know.
But why didn't you
come to me back then?
I could've helped.
Because...
I was scared.
Of what?
I was scared that I would
turn out just like him.
So I ran.
To protect you.
From me.
Sam...
you could never be like him.
- You're so high right now.
- I'm so high right now.
I'm not even gonna lie.
I love you.
I love you too.
So what do we do now?
What nobody ever does
in these situations.
We're gonna get the fuck
out of Woodsboro.
- That's her?
- Yeah.
Samantha?
It's Sam.
- I'm...
- I know who you are.
I hope you're okay.
- Listen. I'm sorry...
- You're Billy's daughter.
We'll bring the car around.
Yeah. I'm his daughter.
I'm sorry
if that's weird for you.
No. no. it's...
I've been through this.
A lot.
You want to talk?
I appreciate it.
And I'm...
I'm really sorry about Dewey.
But I'm taking my sister away
from all this.
I tried running too.
It doesn't work.
it always follows.
All due respect.
that's your life. not mine.
- I'm not so sure about that.
- What do you want from me. lady?
Hey! Watch your tone.
new girl.
You know how they always say
it goes back to the original?
Here's the original.
I want your help.
Because you're wrong.
this is your life now.
Which means whoever this is
will keep coming for you.
- So?
- So I want you to help us kill him.
You want me to help you and the host
of a morning show commit murder?
- Correct.
- Yeah.
And I'm what
in this scenario?
The bait?
The helpless victim?
- If the shoe fits...
- You're not helpless. Sam.
He killed your friend.
he killed ours.
And I have kids. which means I won't
sleep until he's in the ground.
Look. I'm sorry about what
this has done to your lives.
But no matter what you
or the killer or anyone says.
this isn't my story.
All right!
Let's get the fuck out of town.
huh?
Sorry.
That's my boyfriend. Richie.
Nice to meet... We met.
Sam. please get in the car so we
never have to see these people again.
- Sam...
- No. We're leaving.
That's the only way
I can protect Tara.
Okay. good luck.
You too.
Well.
that went fucking horribly.
Don't worry. I have a plan.
She seems really tough.
Honestly. Sid.
who gives a shit?
You said it yourself.
he's gonna go after her.
I put a tracker
on her car.
- You did what?
- It seemed like something
Gale Weathers would do.
Take that as a compliment.
I left a message for Mom.
I told her where we're going.
Fuck. where is it?
Where's what?
My inhaler.
I usually keep an extra one.
Should we go back?
Whoa. Okay.
I vote for not going back
to the murder hospital.
- You want to stop at a pharmacy?
- I'd need a prescription.
But I left an extra one
at Amber's.
- Her house is on the way.
- No. No. No. no. no.
I'd be in and out.
Could you hold out
till Modesto?
- I don't think so.
- Okay. what's the address?
123 No Fucking Way Lane.
Richie. she needs it.
And I need to keep all the
blood inside my body. So do you.
Richie. please.
It's okay.
Okay. yeah. Fuck.
What's the goddamn address?
Keep pouring. Wheeler.
Thank you.
Hey.
To Wes!
Beautiful son of a bitch.
We love you. buddy!
Shots. really?
This is supposed to be a memorial.
Well. this is how I mourn
and distract myself from
the looming specter of Death.
Hey. we're low on beer.
There's more in the basement.
I'll go get some.
What the fuck. Mindy?
Jesus!
That was a test.
And you failed.
Never go off on your own
with a masked killer around.
You're the one that said
we needed more beer.
And you should have asked me
to come with you.
You know what else
you shouldn't do
when there's
a masked killer around?
What?
Follow someone into
a dark. creepy basement alone.
I mean...
...how do you know
I'm not the killer?
Because I am.
I'm not. actually.
But let that be a lesson.
Don't trust anyone.
Then how can I trust you when
you say you're not the killer?
Exactly.
You're learning.
Now let's go back
upstairs.
You first.
Very good.
I think... Think I'm ready.
I mean. I think we should.
Like now.
You want to go upstairs?
Like... Like upstairs?
Uh-huh. Right now.
Um...
Don't take this the wrong way.
but I think I have to pass on that.
What?
Why?
You know. I'm not like entirely
sure that you're not the...
killer.
"Don't take this
the wrong way"?
No. no. look. I'm almost 100%
certain that you are not.
but the safest option
is to be down here
with all the people...
Fuck you.
...and the potential witnesses.
That is a completely valid
emotional response to have.
- That too.
- Fucking asshole.
Good job.
Fuck you. Mindy.
If I hadn't have written
that book about your mother.
- none of this would've happened.
- Gale.
- I started all of this.
- No. you didn't.
Billy Loomis started this.
and we're gonna end it.
After tonight.
no more books.
no more movies.
no more fucking Ghostface.
- Don't you know the rules?
- What rules?
There are specific rules
that one must abide by to
successfully survive a horror movie.
For instance.
number one...
Don't do it.
Don't go outside after her.
She's not texting me back.
Because she's probably dead.
Jesus. Mindy.
That's my girlfriend.
and I love her.
Was your girlfriend.
You're just gonna sit and watch a
movie about our uncle getting stabbed?
It calms me down. okay?
I'm also gonna smoke some weed
and possibly
hook up with Frances.
Have fun.
Oh. my God. at least take
some sort of weapon.
Here you go.
All right.
What?
Ah.
Liv?
All right.
Okay. yeah. no.
Shit!
Fuck!
Please. please. please.
Whoa! Stop! Wait!
Oh. perfect.
She's having a party.
Who has a party in the
middle of a killing spree?
- Look. I'm aborting the plan.
- No. we're already here.
I'll go in quickly and get it.
I'll be back in five.
I'm coming too.
If you think I'm waiting
out here
just to get murdered.
you're out of your mind.
Tara!
What are you doing
out of the hospital?
Should you even be up
and around?
- I need my spare inhaler.
- Why? Where are you going?
It's fine. Don't tell me.
I get it. Just be safe. okay?
I think it's in my room.
All right. everyone!
Thanks for coming.
but the party's over!
- Time to go!
- Why?
But it's so early!
Let's go.
Hey. hey. hey! Hello!
Can we cut the music. please?
Uh. hi... Gen Z.
How are you? Um...
Both Sam and Tara here have been
attacked by the killer twice.
And now they're here. which makes
this place a huge murder target. so...
if I were you.
I would probably leave.
Okay. I tried to be nice.
Get the fuck out!
Please get the fuck out.
- Sincerely. get the fuck out.
- Buzzkill!
Thank you. Thank you all.
I'm saving your life. I promise.
Thanks. teens.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for leaving the cup.
Thank you.
Saving your life.
I'm saving your life.
Saving your life. thank you.
And number three:
Never. ever. ever.
under any circumstances.
say. "I'll be right back."
'Cause you won't be back.
Hey.
somebody's goofy-ass dad's kicking us out.
Goddamn it.
Thank you.
Thanks. guys.
have a good night.
- You have my number.
- Bye.
Bye.
Hi. Uh...
Is there any beer left?
There's none in the kitchen.
Yes. Richie.
there's beer in the basement.
Right behind you.
Basement.
Yeah.
Do you want to. uh.
come with me?
No. But you were right to ask.
Yeah. Um...
Okay. I'll be right back...
Aha!
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Okay.
Well. he's dead.
The goddamn fucking Uber
canceled on me!
Great.
Now I can't have sex.
and I can't get a ride home.
Could this night
get any shittier?
Liv. where's my brother?
What? I don't know. Mindy.
Probably off accusing everyone
of being the killer!
He actually went looking
for you.
I didn't see him.
Okay?
Why are you looking at me
like that?
Just revising my suspect list.
Fuck this!
Are you afraid of me.
Mindy?
You think I did something
to your brother? Huh?
You think I'm gonna...
cut you up?
A little bit now...
yeah.
I thought you said I was
too boring to be the killer.
Maybe that's the twist.
What do you think. huh?
You're the expert.
You know what eventually happens
to the expert?
What?
Enjoy your stupid movie.
Fucking psycho.
They stopped.
- Gas station?
- No. I...
- Oh. shit.
- What?
Oh. shit. How far are we?
Too far.
Damn it.
Tara. we're leaving!
Hello.
You need to get out
of that house right now.
How do you know where I am?
You're in Stu Macher's house.
where your dad and Stu
killed everyone.
Someone planned
to get you there.
You need to get the fuck out.
Sam!
No. Jamie. Watch out.
Watch out. Jamie.
You know he's around.
- What?
- There he is.
Come on. man. turn around!
Turn around! Dude!
I told you.
I told you. he's around the corner.
Jamie.
- Look behind you.
- No. Randy. look behind you.
Come on. man.
turn around!
Dude. what are you doing?
You can do it!
These are your rules!
Own that shit.
Behind you! Turn around.
Look behind...
Oh. shit!
- Mindy.
- That's a lot of blood. Sam.
No. Mindy. stay with me.
What did you do to her?
Nothing.
No. I didn't do anything.
- The killer. he...
- Mindy!
What the fuck?
Richie. where the fuck were you?
I went into the basement
to get beer.
You went to the basement alone?
I asked her to come with me!
She said no!
Fuck!
Stay the fuck back.
Jesus Christ!
I was with Tara.
but the rest of you
were wandering around.
One of you
is the fucking killer!
Fuck you. Amber. Fuck you!
Why is there blood
on your hands?
What?
I found Chad.
- I found Chad and he's...
- Chad?
- You're fucking lying.
- No.
- You're the killer.
- No. I'm not.
Liv. stop.
- Fuck you!
- Liv. just stop!
Fuck you. Amber.
I'm not the fucking killer!
I know.
Welcome to act three.
Run!
Holy shit!
- Sam. come on!
- No...
Run! Go. go. go! Go!
Oh. my God.
Holy shit!
- Oh. my God... Tara!
- Wait. no. Sam.
- She has a gun.
- Richie.
There are always
two killers.
Sam. please put the knife down.
Look. I think...
- The other killer might be Tara.
- What?
She's the one
that brought us here.
and you two have been
estranged for years.
I mean.
how well
do you really know her?
Better than I know you.
Sam. wait. whoa. Sam!
Sounds about right.
You ready?
For this? Never.
Here we go.
Help me. help me! He stabbed me!
- What do you think?
- Trap.
Fuck it.
Ow!
Gale! Gale!
Wait. Let me see.
Let me see.
- You got to go to the hospital.
- No.
You said we were gonna finish
this. Go finish it. Sidney.
Gale.
For Dewey.
Anyone hiding.
killer or not.
you have five seconds
to show yourself!
Oh. Tara.
Oh. my God.
Sam.
Sam. please.
Hello. Sidney!
Hello there.
Where'd you go?
Oh. this isn't Amber.
I'm the other one.
Oh. There's two of you. Again.
I've seen this movie before.
Not this movie. Sidney.
You really need
some new material.
I got you here. didn't I?
You might actually be
the most derivative one of all.
I mean. Christ.
the same house?
Maybe so.
But you forgot the first rule
of surviving a Stab movie.
Never answer the...
- I'm bored.
- Wait!
Put your hands up!
Show me your hands!
What are you doing in there?
- Hiding from murderers.
- I told you to come out!
I'm not gonna come out!
You're shooting everything!
Holy shit.
it's Ghostface!
Richie! Gun. Get the gun.
Yeah. kind of hard
since you shot me in the leg.
Fuck. Fuck.
- Yes! Yes!
- Shoot him!
Thank God you're okay.
'Cause I really.
really wanted to be
the one to kill you.
Sit the fuck down. Prescott!
I can't believe this worked.
I know.
It's a bummer it's me.
But it really was
the best choice for the movie.
This isn't a fucking movie!
No. But it will be.
- That's the point. right. Amber?
- Right. hon!
Third act bloodbath. check.
Killers revealed. check.
Time for the big finale!
- Richie...
- Shh. shh...
Okay. Okay.
Let's get 'em
into the kitchen.
Let's go. bitch!
Someone has to
save the franchise.
You see. no one has made a great
Stab movie since the first one.
Not really.
Hey. baby. you want to go get
- the very ex-Mrs. Riley?
- Yeah. I do.
Hey. hey!
Whoa... whoa.
Sidney Prescott.
You know...
I'm a really big fan.
Go fuck yourself.
You see the last Stab movie?
Not really a fan
of scary movies.
That checks out.
Anyway. it sucked balls.
Because nobody takes
the true fans seriously.
Not really.
They just laugh at us. and why?
Because we love something?
We're just a fucking joke
to them?
How can fandom be toxic?
It's about love!
They don't fucking understand that
these movies are important to people.
- Richie...
- We're gonna help them!
Hollywood's
totally fucking out of ideas.
so we decided we'd give them some
new source material to follow.
You know.
bring it back to basics.
Because that's how you make
a great Stab movie. Sam.
"Based on actual events."
- Gale.
- Shh. shh.
Back up. Back up.
You did all this
just to make me the hero
of your fucked-up movie?
Sweetie. you're not the hero.
You're the villain.
The daughter of Billy Loomis
who sees fucked-up visions
of her dead dad?
Sidney Prescott
killed your father.
You...
did all this just to get her
back to Woodsboro.
You know what the biggest
problem
with the Stab movies is?
There's no Michael Myers
or Jason Voorhees.
No bad guy to keep coming back.
But the illegitimate daughter
of the original mastermind?
Now that's a fucking villain.
- How did you know?
- About your father?
It's a small town.
and your mom's a drunk!
I met Richie
on the Stab subreddit.
I've been obsessed ever since
my parents bought this house.
We realized pretty quickly
we had similar ideas.
Wasn't that hard for me
to find you in Modesto.
It wasn't that hard for me
to fuck you. either.
But I guess
being a sexually available woman
is supposed to be empowering
these days.
Fuck you!
Well. now you're just
quoting the original.
But it wouldn't work
with just you. Sam.
See. we had to bring the legacy
characters back to make it matter.
Can't have a bona fide Halloween
without Jamie Lee!
Nope!
Dewey had to die
to make it real.
To show that this
wasn't just some bullshit.
cash-in. run-of-the-mill sequel.
Because our movie
has fucking stakes!
'Cause anyone can die
in a requel.
No!
Goddamn it. Whoa. whoa!
No. hey! Sit the fuck down.
I'm so sorry. Sid.
We can't let you live either.
I mean.
surviving this many times...
that would just be ridiculous.
This time the fans are gonna be
the ones who win.
- That about cover it?
- Nailed it. baby.
Get Tara out of the closet.
We got to start staging
the bodies!
Stay with me. Sid.
Stay with me.
You really
should've listened to Dewey.
He nailed it in one!
Dude. look at the love interest!
Are you fucking stupid?
I even had you convinced
it could be your sister.
Um. she's not here.
What the fuck do you mean.
"She's not here"?
She's not here!
I untied her.
Guess you're not
as persuasive as you thought.
That's for you.
Yeah.
Like your gimpy little sister's
gonna make a difference.
She's our fucking pincushion
at this point.
Amber! Fan out.
She couldn't have gotten far.
I can't find her!
Amber?
Sam! Where you going?
Your big scene's coming up!
Fucking kill you!
The fucking hand sanitizer?
No. no. no. it's not my fault!
It's not my fault!
Let me guess.
the movies made you do it?
No. it was the message boards!
I was radicalized.
- By movie fans?
- Yes. they're so mad!
Please. it's not my fault.
I'm just a dumb kid.
I wanted to be
a part of something.
"A part of something"?
You killed my best friend!
Yeah. and he died like a pussy.
That's the thing about slashers.
Sam.
So many blood trails.
This one yours?
Only one way to find out!
I was the last thing Dewey saw
before he died too.
I can't believe
I get to do you both.
No last-minute saves this time.
Your story's over!
Time to pass the torch.
It's all yours. bitch!
- You want to do the honors?
- This one's yours.
No. stop. stop. stop!
I'm sorry about Dewey.
Fuck you.
Enjoy that torch.
Stop...
fucking up...
my ending!
Sam?
Sam!
Okay.
What are you gonna do now. huh?
Make a scary phone call to me?
Pop out of that closet
in a Ghostface mask?
No.
Because you're the villain!
And the villain dies at the end.
Those are the rules.
I'm introducing
a new rule.
And what would that be? Huh?
Well?
Never fuck with
the daughter of a serial killer.
Wait!
What about... my ending?
Here it comes.
No!
Careful.
they always come back.
Okay. then.
I still prefer The Babadook.
Are you okay?
- Are you good?
- Mm-hmm.
I'm so sorry.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. sir.
- Hey.
She's gonna be okay.
Can you take us to a
different hospital this time?
Of course.
You ready to go?
I'll be right back. yeah?
Your vitals look good.
Just sit tight
for a draft. okay?
Sidney. Gale.
Thank you both.
For everything.
Are you gonna be all right?
I'll survive.
I always do.
You were right...
about not running.
Sorry about that.
How are you doing?
Ask me in a few days.
But at least I know
what I'm gonna write about.
What's that?
Not this.
Those fuckers can die
in anonymity.
But maybe something
about a good man
who used to be
the sheriff here once.
I'd like to read that story.
Can I ask you a weird question?
Yeah.
Am I gonna be okay?
Eventually.
- Hey.
- Wait. Sam. Sam. Sam!
Thank you.
Well. you're not going
anywhere without me.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna hold your hand
all the way there.
I can take care of her
and her sister.
She's all ready
for transportation.
Twenty-five years ago.
almost to the day. in this very house
a tragic story ended.
Tonight. a new chapter
came to a close.
Police do not have
a lot of information right now.
as they are still
collecting evidence.
As you can see. this is
a very active crime scene here.
An unknown number of fatalities.
several injuries.
some people being taken off by
ambulance right now as we speak.
This is a developing story...
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull